Hey, Flanders, when are your busy hours?
Oh, I expect things to start picking up soon.
I think word of mouth is starting to spread.
Hey, I hear you validate parking tickets without purchase.
Oh, right is rain. Or as we say around here, left is rain.
Just stamp the ticket.
Oh, okay.
Hello, Governor. Lube job while you white?
Don't touch me.
20% off at Lullabies.
This tall and big baby sent you.
I know you can hear me. I'm talking to you.
You sicken me.
Your teenage son or daughter will think this wishbone necklace is really cool.
I doubt my son or daughter is that stupid.
No.
I need one 29-cent stamp.
That's $1.85.
I want $2 worth of gas, please.
How much is your petty candy?
Surprisingly expensive.
What a ripoff.
This is what I think of your store.
You're a jerk.
I did it. Second in line and all I had to do was miss eight days of work.
With the money you would have made working, you could have bought tickets from a scalper.
In theory, yes. Jerk.
The shine on my shoulders makes me happy.
Sir, hello, sir.
Yes, you look like a man who needs help satisfying his wife.
Who controls the British crown?
Who keeps the metric system down?
We do.
Who links Atlantis off the maps?
Who keeps the Martians under wraps?
We do.
Who holds back the electric car?
Who makes the Gutenberg a sark?
We do.
Who robscape fish of their sight?
Who rigs every Oscar night?
We do.
Thank you.
And as a final humiliation, you must walk home naked, dragging behind you the stone of shame.
The mark.
Oh, there. It's just a birthmark, and I'll thank you not to stare.
He's the chosen one.
You are the chosen one, whom the sacred parchment prophesied would lead us to glory.
Now, to the top of Mount Springfield for the coronation, remove the stone of shame.
Woohoo!
Attach the stone of triumph.
Oh!
Yay!
Here, let me gift wrap that for you.
Mind if I tidy you up a bit while you wait?
Help yourself to a piece of candy from that bowl.
I'll just comb your hair.
Stop it, stop it.
Cancel my purchase. I'll just learn to be right-handed.
Sorry, I drove him away.
No, it was me. I don't give anyone a moment's peace. I'm a monster.
Why don't we start out with some questions from the audience? Yes, yes, you, sir.
Yeah, why does this show feel like it's 20 years out of date?
Because...wait, could you repeat that?
Yes, I said I love the show and so does my family. And camera three.
Come back, come back! Willie still loves you, oh great one!
Just fill out this form and you're on your way to the reserve.
There's a question that's crossed out.
Well, due to a recent presidential order, we're not allowed to ask that particular question.
Well I think I can make it out. Are you a homosexual...
For God's sake, don't answer that. I could go to jail.
But I'm not a homosexual...
La la la la la, I am not listening, la la la la la la la la la la.
Nice fella. I wonder if he's gay.
Hey everybody look! Herman Tim's area is back!
You idiots! She meant we should disperse!