Good news about the Esplanade, the legislature has voted to refund the special Newark Development
District along Freeling-Hisen Avenue north from the Museum of Trucking.
Because of the vote, Omni is going to put up a hotel with a Galleria on the first floor.
Word came down yesterday.
A Galleria?
Fifty stores selling sneakers and turnip greens?
It's a demographic imperative.
Hoboken's maxed out.
The Prada people are already moving to Down Neck.
Where are they going to go next?
You know, my old man, he had a piece of the garbage transfer station in Lower Manhattan
back in the 70s.
That people told him.
Stopped buying up the abandoned buildings around here, but he couldn't see it.
And now it's Tribeca.
I tell you, Tony, I'm borrowing money myself to grab up parcels along Freeling-Hisen Avenue
through a shell company.
And a private citizen like you, who's going to quibble with patriotic entrepreneurism?
My uncle has property down on Freeling-Hisen.